Hello friends, welcome to
your own channel ST Study 247. So
friends, in this video we are going to discuss
stock market quick news. We will quickly discuss all the
news of the stock market today.
So friends,
you can see that today we again saw a great rise in Nifty 50. Today we have seen
Nifty 50 closing with a rise of 144 points.
You can see that
in the middle, the high of Nifty 50
was around 1318 points.
Today we have also seen the closing around the same level. So,
in the middle, you must have seen that
Nifty had also made a low around 12962,
but after that, we have again
seen a sudden high today. So friends, the main
reason was that Moderna announced that
their vaccine is 100%
effective against the severe patients of Covid-19. So, due to this also,
we have seen a little excitement in the market today.
If we look at the BSE Sensex,
then the BSE  The Sensex is also seeing a spectacular
rally of over 500 points and on a closing
basis, a closing of 4465 5.44 was seen,
which we can say is a spectacular
closing. In between, you can see that the
BSE Sensex had also gone down a lot to the
level of 44118. So friends, you can see that the
domestic equity market ended over
1 per high. Basically, what you must have seen today is a
rally in Bharti stock. You
can see from Aaaa Bank.
[Music]
I like DV Slap company
because if you look at its pre-COVID
setup, look at the pre-COVID chart pattern,
you will see that it is increasing a lot, it is
in a long-term trend, that is, it is
in an increasing trend. So friends, if I
talk about some companies like Aarti Drugs, Lori
Slap, then these companies are those pharma companies
which, you will see, before COVID, no one
even recognized these companies so much.
They
picked up growth only later and gave very good
returns. But if I talk about DV Slack
or Dr Lal Path  These companies were
performing well even before COVID
and are still performing well.
You
can see that they recently
set up a manufacturing facility
in Andhra Pradesh. This is excellent news
for the company. The company already
showed excellent results in the second quarter, so it is
possible that we may see the company performing even better in the coming time.
Today, we
also got good news from Indian Hotels. Indian Hotels is
signing three new Taj hotels. You
can see that Indian Hotels has also
signed three new Taj hotels here today. You
can see that Indian Hotels Company is growing at Rs
120 per room at 2.08 after the company announced the
signing of three Taj hotels – two in Kolkata, one in
West Bengal, and one in Patna, Bihar.
You can see that the company is growing brilliantly here.
But I
want to ask how is the hotel business because
as soon as the news of COVID comes
in the market, then what happens is that this
hotel business takes a little beating.  It can be
seen that the company is good, there
is no problem in Indian Hotel Company,
but I want to say that right now,
until the situation of Covid-19 is
resolved, you can stay away from hotels and
entertainment related stocks
like PVR and these stocks.
Coming to the next news, what is the next news,
by Bharti Tel target price of Rs 650
Motilal Oswal, you
can see again today, today on this very date
they have updated, they have
again given a new target rating to Bharti Tel, you
see the target price has been set up for
650, you can see here that the current
market price of Bharti Tel is 469
when this target was announced, even today at
closing you saw that Bharti
Tel is closing around 479, friends, the
next news related to you is
Tata's year end currently holds the third
position in the Indian market in terms of
sale concern, so this is good news from Tata.
You can see that in Covid,
so I want to say that
even from the company's side, we had seen excellent
commentary that they would make the company debt free,
so if you want, you
can also keep your eye on the stock, let's
come to the next news on
reliance.com, if you want to do
some buying, value investing, then
you can
also look at reliance1, all the
reliance.com cap shares had gone
down a lot today, the next news is
related to Escorts, so friends, if you like the
company, then you
can definitely stay in it, so
what happens is Dispina Sell on Escorts Shell Fly 3,
sometimes the operator puts a lot of selling orders here,
after which we
see such things, but the company
is a fundamentally strong company for the long term, if you want, you can keep this company in your eye
or keep it in the buy list,
if you find the stock at an even lower level,
then I want to say that you
can also take the help of your financial advisor, so you can look at
Dispina Sell on Escorts Share Fly 3,
so we  We had seen that it had shown a great recovery, so if you
want, you should
definitely keep this company in your eye. Let's come to the next
news, it is related to ICICI Lombard. So
friends, Lombard stock
hits record high on not to acquire
Indian AXA General Insurance. So this company is
acquiring Indian AXA General Insurance.
As soon as this news came in the media,
Shardar Kam stock showed a rise and
also hit an all-time high of 1500 around 3 o'clock. The
chart pattern of the company is
also in an up trend and if you look at the old time, it is
in increasing order. So if you
want, you can keep an eye on this company also.
Basically, whatever their initial
acquisition was, they have made
efforts to complete it,
after which we are seeing this rise. So you
can see that ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company shares hit a new all-
time high after the company received in-
principal approval to acquire Indian AXA
General Insurance. Another positive news today was
also from Moderna.  Apart from the vaccine, the
economists
upgraded the GDP for the first time after the
quarter two surprise. So, in quarter two,
we saw how our
GDP was seen
declining.
Some positivity was seen here,
positive sentiments were seen
due to which we saw the market rising today.
Next news can be seen,
after Tata Motors, there is TVS Motor.
TVS Motor Guess after November sales cross
20 per year on year. Friends, all these
companies which are related to motor are
related to auto sector, that is why we
saw sales increasing in them because it was the
festive season of October-November, there
people did a lot of shopping during Diwali and Dussehra.
So if you want, you can keep
TVS Motor in your buy list.
I think you should
take the help of your financial advisor and the company has
definitely shown a great recovery here. We will have to
see in the coming time how the company
shows further recovery here. Next news is
maintained on
hdfc0000008. It has given in the life sector like
ADAC.  I like Life and SBI Life
companies because many
people were not aware earlier that they would need to take
some health care or some policy due to a disease like Covid
because no one was aware of Corona, so
now many people have become cautious,
many people want to improve themselves, that is why they will take
more and more
health insurance policies due to which
they will have to pay premium and when they pay
premium, these
companies definitely generate some revenue, the
next news from there is
related to Vodafone-Idea, you have already
gone, you can see there is
an article in Business Today, the issue was recently discussed at a
meeting in which PM Modi was also
present, but the final decision will most likely be
taken in the next meeting after
being in pros and cons, so you
can see that this decision can be taken after looking at some pros and cons
and this has
already been discussed with Modi ji,
so we will have to see what the government lost in September
We get to see high profile international tax arbitrations happening here,
so we will get to see all those things in the future.
Currently, all these things have been
put up in front of PM Modi.
Next up is Vodafone-Idea hikes
prices of two postpaid plans. Prepaid
hike in the coming time. So, Vodafone-Idea has
increased its postpaid plans here and its
prepaid plans can also be seen increasing.
In the coming time, you
can see that Vodafone-Idea has now increased its postpaid plans by
Rs 598 and Rs
749 family postpaid plans by Rs 50. So,
they have increased their postpaid plans by Rs 50.
Now you can see that
these plans now cost Rs 649 and Rs 799.
Respectively, we are testing waters with
high-end postpaid plans and it is the
tariff hike in the mass market plans of Rs 56
and Rs 84.  Days plan which will be the game
changer said Rajeev Sharma, Head of Research at
SBI Cap. So we have to see how
this company monitors its postpaid plans after postpaid,
whether there is a tariff hike there too,
if there is a tariff hike
then do those customers
shift to Bharti or not, all these things have to be
seen. Next news is the idea of
expecting Vodafone-Idea to lead with
tariff, so the way Vodafone-Idea is
tertiary here, if the other two
companies have not done it then do they also
get to increase the tariff on vodafoneidea.com
or not, if they also increase it then
definitely all three companies can come into competition. Let's
see the reliance1 news,
Bharti at t share surge price hike by
vodafoneidea.com
search 3.5 to 471 while wad fun ia rose 2 per
to 99.98
reliance.com stocks  Which I have covered
and if we see today's data
of FII and FPI,
they have done a great deal of buying here,
you can see they bought for
11337 crores only but they sold for
8095 crores and you can see the net
value is in positive for 3242 crores, at the same time
DI sold a lot of goods today, you can see worth
1043 crores, here we have seen net selling, here we saw
net
buying, whenever FII and
FPI buy here, the
market trends always go towards the bulls,
this is a hint which you can follow, so
friends, that was all in this video,
we will meet very soon
with the next video and thank you very much for giving me your valuable time, so
thank you so much